## **COREY DUNKIN**

Senior Front End Developer

I am a developer who is always looking to expand my skills and use them in interesting and challenging ways.

## **ABOUT ME**

I am a **Senior Front End Developer** who has worked on various high traffic, intricate websites for large-scale clients such as **Macquarie Bank, NBNco, McDonalds, Volkswagen and the Australian Defence Force**.

I am highly proficient in HTML5, CSS3, and Advanced Javascript. I have extensive knowledge in building and maintaining projects utilising Javascript frameworks such as Angular 7+/React and CSS frameworks such as Bootstrap/Foundation and have personally set up various projects and their components using build tools such as Node, Gulp and Grunt to help compile, minify and enchance the Javascript, SASS and HTML.

I have worked at maintaining and sharing the code of such large-scale sites by using source control tools such as Git and Bitbucket and have been responsible for documenting my work using Confluence and responding to various briefs for projects using Jira within a team in both an Agile and Waterfall setting while also executing these Stakeholder needs within sprints.

## **KNOWLEDGE AND SKILS**

Languages / Tech	Frameworks / APIs	Apps / Tools
HTML/HTML5	Angular 7+	Node
JS	React	Gulp
CSS/CSS3	Backbone.js	Grunt
SASS/SCSS	Bootstrap	Bower
LESS	jQuery	BrowserSync
Java	CreateJS	GIT
Node.js	GSAP	Bitbucket
Canvas	Wordpress	IntelliJ
SVGs/Icons/Fonts	Facebook	Sublime Text
PHP	Google Maps	Sketch
SQL	Youtube	Jira
	WEM	Confluence
	AEM	Adobe Photoshop

## CONTACTS

hello@coreydunkin.com

in linkedin.com/in/coreydunkin

**)** +61 434 090 596

www.coreydunkin.com

**REFERENCES** 

Available upon request

# COREY DUNKIN

Senior Front End Developer

I am a developer who is always looking to expand my skills and use them in interesting and challenging ways.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Present Feb 2018

#### SENIOR FRONT END DEVELOPER

NBNco

I was hired as part of NBNco at the start of 2018 as a Senior Front End Developer and during my time have so far been responsible for working on, upgrading and maintaining their high-traffic NBN roll-out map with the UI/Maps team which requires extensive knowledge in such Front End technologies such as Angular, Javascript, SASS, Bootstrap, Google Maps API and Node. I was also taken on board for my knowledge in the CMS framework AEM which is what the website is built upon and my ability to work inside Java along with the Back End Developers.

Since working on the Roll-out map, I have moved on to work with the Forms team that is responsible for maintaining, building and upgrading the various high-traffic forms that are located throughout the website. These forms are built using Typescript within Angular 7+, styled in SASS within Bootstrap and hooked into the front-facing website using Java within AEM. These new components would be maintained using Git and knowledge would be shared using Jira/ Confluence. Finally, Jasmine would be utilised to write unit tests for our new components to ensure proper upkeep was maintained.

In both scenarios I worked in an Agile setting, responding and liasing with Stakeholders to help come up with solutions to their needs and executing these solutions within two week sprints.

Feb 2018 Mar 2016

### SENIOR FRONT END DEVELOPER

Macquarie Group

As part of the Macquarie Group team. I was responsible for upgrading, maintaining, scoping out and building new components for the Macquarie Bank front-facing website.

During my time there I was part of a team that helped in upgrading the JS framework of the website from AngularJS to Angular 5 along with upgrading the CSS to SASS, while utilising GULP as the build/compile tool in minifying and exporting the code into AEM while also introducing source control in the form of Bitbucket.

Our projects were often discussed with us by various Stakeholders and Business Analysts where we would be given an objective (eg. drive traffic towards Home Loans and increase our Home Loans by 15%), these objectives would be fleshed out by the developers and myself in how we could achieve such tasks. We would then carry out in executing various plans that would be performed over the sprint(s).

### **CONTACTS**

hello@coreydunkin.com

**)** +61 434 090 596

in linkedin.com/in/coreydunkin

www.coreydunkin.com

**REFERENCES** 

Available upon request

## **COREY DUNKIN**

Senior Front End Developer

I am a developer who is always looking to expand my skills and use them in interesting and challenging ways.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

2015-2016 ♦ SENIOR WEB DESIGNER

Big Mobile

Responsible for designing and building various mobile web apps, websites, adverts, responsive builds and other various applications for a large range of clients.

2014 - 2015 ♦ FRONT-END DEVELOPER

HAVAS

I was responsible for building responsive HTML5 websites using jQuery, AngularJS, Bower, Gulp, Grunt, SASS and LESS for clients such as the Australian Defence Force, Telstra, Activia and various other clients.

2011 - 2014 ♦ WEB DESIGNER/FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Tribal DDB

Responsible for designing and building the front-end for various desktop and mobile websites, email newsletters, banner adverts and various applications for clients such as Volkswagen, Telstra, Audi and McDonalds.

2010 - 2011 ♦ **DIGITAL DESIGNER/DEVELOPER** 

Elastic Digital

Responsible for various design and development jobs across websites for clients such as Optus, VMware and Symantec.

2009 - 2010 ♦ GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Mahlab Media

I was a Junior Graphic Designer who worked on various publications for Mahlab Media and was also tasked with designing their website.

Present FREELANCE DESIGNER/DEVELOPER

Freelance

Various freelance jobs. Including identity design, branding, and website work.

**EDUCATION** 

2007 - 2008 ◆ ST GEORGE DESIGN COLLEGE

Advanced Diploma

2005 - 2007 ◆ ST GEORGE DESIGN COLLEGE

Diploma

2005 - 2008 **♦ SEMI PERMANENT** 

Volunteer helper/organiser

**CONTACTS** 

hello@coreydunkin.com

**)** +61 434 090 596

in linkedin.com/in/coreydunkin

www.coreydunkin.com

**REFERENCES** 

Available upon request